realtyna.com 2019-09-27

# Realtyna Privacy Policy Statement

This privacy statement describes how Realtyna® L.L.C. collects and uses the personal information you provide on our Web site:  
[realtyna.com](https://realtyna.com/). It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information.

Realtyna® L.L.C. has been awarded TRUSTe’s Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with [TRUSTe’s program requirements](https://www.truste.com/privacy-program-requirements/index.html)  
including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information. TRUSTe’s mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at http://support.realtyna.com If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact [TRUSTe here](https://www.truste.com/about_TRUSTe/contact_us.html)

The TRUSTe program covers only information that is collected through this Web site, and does not cover information that may be collected through software downloaded from the site.

###### Collection and Use of Personal Information

###### We collect the following personal information from you:

  * Contact Information such as name, email address, mailing address, phone number
  * Preferences Information you provide such as product or content interests, or communication or marketing preferences
  * Usage activity about how you interact with us such as purchase history, what content you viewed, and which areas of our site you visited.

###### We also collect the following information from you:

  * Information about your business such as company name, company size, business type
  * Demographic information such as household income, age, education, gender, interests, and zip code
  * As is true of most Web sites, we automatically gather information about your computer such as your IP address, browser type, referring/exit pages, and  
operating system.

###### We use this information to:

  * Fulfill your order
  * Send you an order confirmation
  * Assess your needs to determine suitable products or services
  * Send you requested product or service information
  * Send product updates or warranty information
  * Respond to customer service requests
  * Administer your account
  * Send you marketing communications
  * Administer contests and sweepstakes you entered, and notify you if you won
  * Improve our Web site and marketing efforts
  * Conduct research and analysis
  * Respond to your questions and concerns
  * Send you a catalog

You may choose to stop receiving our newsletter or marketing emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails or you can contact us at http://support.realtyna.com

Information Obtained from Third Parties

We obtain address information about you from third party sources, such as the US Postal Service, to verify your address so we can properly ship your order to you and to prevent fraud.

If you provide us personal information about others, or if others give us your information, we will only use that information for the specific reason for which it was provided to us.

###### Disclosure to Third Parties

We will share your information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy statement.

We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as shipping your order or offering customer service. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us.

We may disclose your personal information

  * as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process
  * when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request,
  * if Realtyna® L.L.C. is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information, to any other third party with your prior consent to do so.

Checkout

If you choose to use GoogleCheckout to finalize and pay for your order, you will provide your credit card number directly to GoogleCheckout. Google’s  
privacy policy will apply to the information you provide on the GoogleCheckout Web site.

If you choose to use PayPal to finalize and pay for your order, you will provide your credit card number, directly to PayPal. PayPal’s privacy policy will apply to the information you provide on the PayPal Web site.

If you choose to use Amazon to finalize and pay for your order, you will provide your credit card number, directly to Amazon. Amazon’s privacy policy will apply to the information you provide on Amazon’s Web site

Merchant Solutions

This site is hosted by Yahoo! Merchant Solutions. Yahoo! hosts the store pages, ordering system, and collects your billing information directly from you for the purpose of processing that information on our behalf. If you accessed realtyna.com through Yahoo! Shopping, Yahoo! also automatically collects  
information about your shopping experience to allows us better understand who visits the site. Please see the Yahoo! Privacy Policy for more information about how Yahoo! uses this information.

Yahoo! Merchant Solutions uses cookies and log files to track visitors to our site. The statistics collected provide us information about Web site usage.

###### Disclosure to Third Parties

We or a third party contracted by us may use technologies such as cookies, Web beacons, or scripts to gather information about how you and others interact with our Web site. For example, we will know how many users access a specific areas or features within our site and which links or ads they clicked on. We use this aggregated information to understand and optimize how our site is used, improve our marketing efforts, and provide content and features that are of interest to you.

We partner with a third party ad network to either display advertising on our Web site or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our ad network partner uses cookies and Web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information about your activities on this and other Web sites to provide you targeted advertising based upon your interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you targeted ads, you may opt-out by clicking here: [http://preferences.truste.com](http://preferences.truste.com/). Please note this does not opt you out of being served advertising. You will continue to receive generic ads

The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us at http://support.realtyna.com

We provide two means for you to make a purchase on our site. You can either use our order form or a third party checkout option. If you use our shopping cart, the transmission of sensitive information collected on our order form is encrypted using secure socket layer technology (SSL). If you choose to use a third party checkout option to pay for your order, its privacy statement and security practices will apply to your information. We encourage you to read that privacy statement before providing your information.

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us at http://support.realtyna.com . We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

Our Web site includes third party hosted widgets, which are interactive mini-programs that run on our site to provide single-purpose services (e.g. sharing of articles, videos, etc.). Personal information, like your email address, may be collected and cookies may be set so the widget can work properly. The information through the widget is subject to the widget provider’s privacy policy

**Correcting and Updating Your Personal Information**

To review and update your personal information to ensure it is accurate, contact us at http://support.realtyna.com .

**Notification of Privacy Statement Changes**

We may update this privacy statement to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

**Note:** Your email is automatically added to our newsletter when you send us an email. If you wish to opt-out, you can either unsubscribe from the newsletter message or just contact us at support@realtyna.com and request the opt-out.
